<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><ns2:ProductSearchFeed xmlns:ns2="http://www.flipkart.com/affiliate"><products><productInfoList><productBaseInfo><productIdentifier><categoryPaths><categoryPath><item><title>Mobiles&gt;Handsets</title></item></categoryPath></categoryPaths><productId>MOBE6KK93JG5WKB2</productId></productIdentifier><productAttributes><codAvailable>true</codAvailable><color>Black</color><colorVariants>[MOBE6KK9YZJBYGUC]</colorVariants><discountPercentage>15.0</discountPercentage><imageUrls><entry><key>400x400</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/w/t/n/motorola-moto-g-3rd-generation-ap3560ae7k8-400x400-imae9h4h8gkbpq56.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>275x275</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/w/t/n/motorola-moto-g-3rd-generation-ap3560ae7k8-275x275-imae9h4h8gkbpq56.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>75x75</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/w/t/n/motorola-moto-g-3rd-generation-ap3560ae7k8-75x75-imae9h4h8gkbpq56.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>125x125</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/w/t/n/motorola-moto-g-3rd-generation-ap3560ae7k8-125x125-imae9h4h8gkbpq56.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>40x40</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/w/t/n/motorola-moto-g-3rd-generation-ap3560ae7k8-40x40-imae9h4h8gkbpq56.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>1100x1100</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/w/t/n/motorola-moto-g-3rd-generation-ap3560ae7k8-1100x1100-imae9h4h8gkbpq56.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>100x100</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/w/t/n/motorola-moto-g-3rd-generation-ap3560ae7k8-100x100-imae9h4h8gkbpq56.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>200x200</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/w/t/n/motorola-moto-g-3rd-generation-ap3560ae7k8-200x200-imae9h4h8gkbpq56.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>unknown</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/w/t/n/motorola-moto-g-3rd-generation-ap3560ae7k8-original-imae9h4h8gkbpq56.jpeg</value></entry></imageUrls><inStock>true</inStock><maximumRetailPrice><amount>12999.0</amount><currency>INR</currency></maximumRetailPrice><productBrand>Motorola</productBrand><productDescription>Advanced IPX7 water resistance, a 13 MP rear camera and a 5 MP front camera, a long-lasting 2470 mAh battery and Android Lollipop. Meet the beautifully crafted Moto G (3rd Gen), the phone that'll always be there for you. Advanced Water Resistance With the IPX7-rating, the Moto G 3rd Gen is water resistant* enough to handle splashes and accidental drops in water. *Designed to withstand immersion in up to 3 feet of fresh water for up to 30 minutes provided the back cover is properly sealed. Not designed to work while submerged underwater. Do not use while swimming, or subject it to pressurized streams of water. Not dustproof. See Motorola.in for details. Camera The Moto G 3rd Gen features a 13 MP rear camera and a 5 MP front camera. With features such as an ultra-fast f2.0 lens, a color-balancing dual LED flash and HDR, you get perfectly exposed and true-to-life images even in low lighting conditions. Long Lasting Battery The Moto G 3rd Gen comes with a long-lasting 2470 mAh battery* which packs enough juice to last an entire day. Play games, browse the web and listen to music all day without worrying about your phone's battery draining out. *All battery life claims are approximate and based on an average user profile that includes both usage and standby. Actual battery performance will vary and depends on signal strength, network configuration, features selected, and voice, data, operating temperature and other application usage patterns. Performance The Moto G (3rd Gen) boasts a 1.4 GHz Quad-core Qualcomm Snapdragon 410 processor, 2 GB RAM and advanced Adreno graphics. Switch between your favourite apps quickly, enjoy flawless gaming and stream HD videos seamlessly on this Moto smartphone. 4G Stream music, browse the web, play online games and watch videos in a flash, thanks to 4G LTE connectivity. Display A 12.7 cm (5) HD display complements the sleek and stylish design of this Moto smartphone. Immerse yourself in vivid colors and sharp details while viewing photos, watching videos and playing games. Corning Gorilla Glass 3 Corning Gorilla Glass 3 spans your Moto G from nearly end-to-end, protecting your phone from scratches and accidental scrapes. Android OS Enjoy a true Android experience on this smartphone. Moto G runs on the fast and user-friendly Android Lollipop v5.1.1. Dual SIM Juggle between your personal and work life easily by taking advantage of the dual SIM feature of this Moto smartphone. Expandable Storage This phone comes with 16 GB internal storage which can be expanded to an additional 32 GB using a microSD card. Moto Display Preview notifications and updates with Moto Display and decide which ones you want to see. You can even play or pause music* without unlocking your phone. You can also check for new updates on your favourite apps by nudging your phone. *Music controls work with music player apps that use standard Android controls, such as Play Music. Moto Assist Moto Assist keeps track of where you are and what you're doing and adapts accordingly. So if you're in a meeting, it puts your phone in silent mode.  </productDescription><productUrl>http://dl.flipkart.com/dl/moto-g-3rd-generation/p/itme9ysjr7mfry3n?pid=MOBE6KK93JG5WKB2&amp;affid=kanakala8</productUrl><sellingPrice><amount>10999.0</amount><currency>INR</currency></sellingPrice><sizeUnit></sizeUnit><sizeVariants>[MOBE6KK9YZJBYGUC]</sizeVariants><title>Moto G (3rd Generation)</title></productAttributes></productBaseInfo><productShippingBaseInfo/></productInfoList><productInfoList><productBaseInfo><productIdentifier><categoryPaths><categoryPath><item><title>Mobiles&gt;Handsets</title></item></categoryPath></categoryPaths><productId>MOBE8AHABTYGSZ2J</productId></productIdentifier><productAttributes><codAvailable>true</codAvailable><color>Black</color><colorVariants>[MOBE8AHAEG8GFCMX, MOBE8AHAT4SFH3PJ, MOBE9HPZNZRNFDZ2]</colorVariants><discountPercentage>0.0</discountPercentage><imageUrls><entry><key>400x400</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/z/2/j/lenovo-k3-note-na-400x400-imae8hstkr6sbtgt.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>275x275</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/z/2/j/lenovo-k3-note-na-275x275-imae8hstkr6sbtgt.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>75x75</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/z/2/j/lenovo-k3-note-na-75x75-imae8hstkr6sbtgt.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>125x125</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/z/2/j/lenovo-k3-note-na-125x125-imae8hstkr6sbtgt.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>40x40</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/z/2/j/lenovo-k3-note-na-40x40-imae8hstkr6sbtgt.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>1100x1100</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/z/2/j/lenovo-k3-note-na-1100x1100-imae8hstkr6sbtgt.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>100x100</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/z/2/j/lenovo-k3-note-na-100x100-imae8hstkr6sbtgt.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>200x200</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/z/2/j/lenovo-k3-note-na-200x200-imae8hstkr6sbtgt.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>unknown</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/z/2/j/lenovo-k3-note-na-original-imae8hstkr6sbtgt.jpeg</value></entry></imageUrls><inStock>true</inStock><maximumRetailPrice><amount>9999.0</amount><currency>INR</currency></maximumRetailPrice><productBrand>Lenovo</productBrand><productDescription>If you love watching movies or gaming on your smartphone, this sleek and powerful Lenovo K3 Note features a mesmerizing 13.97 cm Full HD display and is backed by powerful Octa Core performance. Display Enjoy watching videos, viewing high-resolution photos and gaming on the big 13.97 cm (5.5) Full HD IPS display of the K3 Note. With the 1920 x 1080 resolution, visuals come to life on this bright and vivid screen. Performance Thanks to the 64-bit Octa Core processor, you can multitask effortlessly on this device. Apps, games, and videos run smoothly and lag-free. This Lenovo device is powered by the faster and smoother Android Lollipop 5.0. Dual SIM Dual Standby Whether you travel abroad often or you want to separate business from pleasure, the Lenovo K3 Note offers you two SIM slots. GSM, WCDMA, and LTE SIM cards are compatible with this device. Battery Run an extra mile before you plug your Lenovo device into the power outlet. The powerful 2900 m Ah battery packs enough punch for you to enjoy non-stop entertainment for longer. Storage With 16 GB internal storage, you can store more of your favorite photos, music and games worry-free in this Lenovo smartphone. Camera The K3 Note packs a 13 MP primary shooter which lets you capture amazing photos and videos. Sensors This Lenovo smartphone features a proximity sensor, gravity sensor, light sensor, anti gyroscope and an electronic compass. The gravity sensor and anti gyroscope let you enjoy flawless motion-based gaming.</productDescription><productUrl>http://dl.flipkart.com/dl/lenovo-k3-note/p/itmebygmmk8cfmy4?pid=MOBE8AHABTYGSZ2J&amp;affid=kanakala8</productUrl><sellingPrice><amount>9999.0</amount><currency>INR</currency></sellingPrice><sizeUnit></sizeUnit><sizeVariants>[MOBE8AHAEG8GFCMX, MOBE8AHAT4SFH3PJ]</sizeVariants><title>Lenovo K3 Note</title></productAttributes></productBaseInfo><productShippingBaseInfo/></productInfoList><productInfoList><productBaseInfo><productIdentifier><categoryPaths><categoryPath><item><title>Mobiles&gt;Handsets</title></item></categoryPath></categoryPaths><productId>MOBE6FT8DZXTBRZZ</productId></productIdentifier><productAttributes><codAvailable>true</codAvailable><color>Black</color><colorVariants>[MOBE7JXXKS6PWW2C, MOBE7JXXQDVZGBHZ, MOBE7JXXWBRAZMSB]</colorVariants><discountPercentage>0.0</discountPercentage><imageUrls><entry><key>400x400</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/r/z/z/lenovo-a6000-plus-a6000-plus-400x400-imae6fyhhrwnaywc.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>75x75</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/r/z/z/lenovo-a6000-plus-a6000-plus-75x75-imae6fyhhrwnaywc.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>275x275</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/r/z/z/lenovo-a6000-plus-a6000-plus-275x275-imae6fyhhrwnaywc.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>125x125</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/r/z/z/lenovo-a6000-plus-a6000-plus-125x125-imae6fyhhrwnaywc.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>40x40</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/r/z/z/lenovo-a6000-plus-a6000-plus-40x40-imae6fyhhrwnaywc.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>1100x1100</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/r/z/z/lenovo-a6000-plus-a6000-plus-1100x1100-imae6fyhhrwnaywc.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>100x100</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/r/z/z/lenovo-a6000-plus-a6000-plus-100x100-imae6fyhhrwnaywc.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>200x200</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/r/z/z/lenovo-a6000-plus-a6000-plus-200x200-imae6fyhhrwnaywc.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>unknown</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/r/z/z/lenovo-a6000-plus-a6000-plus-original-imae6fyhhrwnaywc.jpeg</value></entry></imageUrls><inStock>false</inStock><maximumRetailPrice><amount>7499.0</amount><currency>INR</currency></maximumRetailPrice><productBrand>Lenovo</productBrand><productDescription>Designed for music and multimedia lovers, the Lenovo A6000 Plus is a budget smartphone with a 12.7 cm (5) HD display. It's powered by a quad-core Snapdragon processor which delivers a responsive system performance. Memory &amp; Storage Along with excellent multi-tasking, the 2 GB RAM of this Lenovo device ensures that applications and games run lag-free. The 16 GB ROM easily accommodates all your favorite pictures, music, videos and games. Live Life in HD Powered by a 64-bit quad-core Qualcomm Snapdragon processor, the Lenovo A6000 Plus offers a solid performance at a reasonable price. It's 2300 m Ah battery ensures connectivity with your friends all-day. Twin Speakers Become the DJ at your friend's party with this phone's twin speakers and Dolby Digital Plus audio technology. It provides crisp audio so you can enjoy your music, games and videos. Pair this phone with some good earphones to enjoy the clarity of sound that Dolby provides. 4G LTE Get ultra-fast data transfer speeds on this phone as it supports 4G LTE networks for video streaming and online gaming. Camera This Lenovo smartphone comes with an 8 MP rear camera that clicks great pictures. The 2 MP fixed-focus front camera is good for video calls and selfies. Connectivity Enjoy the flexibility of two SIMs on one phone or choose a separate data plan to save on your phone bills. This is great for people where network coverage varies between telecom providers. Other connectivity features include 3G, Wi-Fi and Bluetooth. Android Operating System With Android KitKat 4.4, you can optimize memory and improve your touch screen responsiveness so that it performs faster than before. This lets you listen to music while you browse a web page with no interruptions or reduced performance. SHAREit with CLONEit This feature allows for sharing of videos, photos and apps across devices without network charges or Wi-Fi. With CLONEit, you can instantly transfer all your old data to you new Lenovo phone. This phone also comes with SYNCit which provides a backup for all your contacts, logs and SMS messages.</productDescription><productUrl>http://dl.flipkart.com/dl/lenovo-a6000-plus/p/itmeb9agnna2thpa?pid=MOBE6FT8DZXTBRZZ&amp;affid=kanakala8</productUrl><sellingPrice><amount>7499.0</amount><currency>INR</currency></sellingPrice><sizeUnit></sizeUnit><sizeVariants>[MOBE7JXXKS6PWW2C, MOBE7JXXWBRAZMSB]</sizeVariants><title>Lenovo A6000 Plus</title></productAttributes></productBaseInfo><productShippingBaseInfo/></productInfoList><productInfoList><productBaseInfo><productIdentifier><categoryPaths><categoryPath><item><title>Mobiles&gt;Handsets</title></item></categoryPath></categoryPaths><productId>MOBE9HWHHTQ3GN9W</productId></productIdentifier><productAttributes><codAvailable>true</codAvailable><color>Black &amp; Champagne</color><discountPercentage>2.0</discountPercentage><imageUrls><entry><key>400x400</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/n/9/w/micromax-canvas-xpress-2-e313-400x400-imae9ztr8zkg3m4z.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>275x275</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/n/9/w/micromax-canvas-xpress-2-e313-275x275-imae9ztr8zkg3m4z.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>75x75</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/n/9/w/micromax-canvas-xpress-2-e313-75x75-imae9ztr8zkg3m4z.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>125x125</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/n/9/w/micromax-canvas-xpress-2-e313-125x125-imae9ztr8zkg3m4z.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>40x40</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/n/9/w/micromax-canvas-xpress-2-e313-40x40-imae9ztr8zkg3m4z.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>1100x1100</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/n/9/w/micromax-canvas-xpress-2-e313-1100x1100-imae9ztr8zkg3m4z.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>100x100</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/n/9/w/micromax-canvas-xpress-2-e313-100x100-imae9ztr8zkg3m4z.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>200x200</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/n/9/w/micromax-canvas-xpress-2-e313-200x200-imae9ztr8zkg3m4z.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>unknown</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/n/9/w/micromax-canvas-xpress-2-e313-original-imae9ztr8zkg3m4z.jpeg</value></entry></imageUrls><inStock>true</inStock><maximumRetailPrice><amount>6349.0</amount><currency>INR</currency></maximumRetailPrice><productBrand>Micromax</productBrand><productDescription>Browse, work or play on the Micromax Canvas Xpress 2 as it comes with a 1.4GHz true Octa Core processor and 1 GB RAM for all your smartphone needs. Download apps on the Play Store or watch a movie on the 12.7cm (5) HD display which renders images from a spectrum of 16 million different colors. Performance This smartphone comes with a 1.4 GHz Cortex A7 processor and 1 GB DDR3 RAM for seamless multitasking and quicker access to your apps and games. With a battery capacity of 2500 m Ah, this phone can last for up to 393 hours on standby. Display Enjoy a movie or stream a video off YouTube on this smartphone's 12.7cm HD display. See every single detail with clarity as this phone displays images from a palette of 16 million colors. Keep scratches at bay as the phone comes with Corning Gorilla Glass 3 with NDR and Oleophobic coating for Fingerprint resistance. Camera Found a great vantage point for pictures? Then grab your Xpress 2 and take great photos on the 13 MP AF BSI Rear Camera with OV sensor and 5P Largan Lens that can also record 1080 p videos. Why not even take a selfie on the phone's 2 MP front camera which comes with OV sensor and Panaroma mode. Connectivity Connect to the internet with 3G connectivity to browse your favorite website or download 9gag on your phone from the Play Store to kill time as this phone connects to Wi-Fi networks. You can also share music or files with other devices using the phone's Bluetooth feature. The smartphone comes loaded with OTG support and E-compass. Storage Store your favorite songs, games or documents on the phone's 8 GB internal memory or expand it by up to 32 GB as it also supports microSD cards.</productDescription><productUrl>http://dl.flipkart.com/dl/micromax-canvas-xpress-2/p/itme9hwhagzzfqua?pid=MOBE9HWHHTQ3GN9W&amp;affid=kanakala8</productUrl><sellingPrice><amount>6199.0</amount><currency>INR</currency></sellingPrice><sizeUnit></sizeUnit><sizeVariants>[]</sizeVariants><title>Micromax Canvas Xpress 2</title></productAttributes></productBaseInfo><productShippingBaseInfo/></productInfoList><productInfoList><productBaseInfo><productIdentifier><categoryPaths><categoryPath><item><title>Mobiles&gt;Handsets</title></item></categoryPath></categoryPaths><productId>MOBECC4UZTSGKWWZ</productId></productIdentifier><productAttributes><codAvailable>true</codAvailable><color>Black</color><colorVariants>[MOBECC4UQTJ5QZFR]</colorVariants><discountPercentage>13.0</discountPercentage><imageUrls><entry><key>400x400</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/w/w/z/motorola-moto-g-turbo-edition-xt1557-400x400-imaechsgw7ndcgdj.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>75x75</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/w/w/z/motorola-moto-g-turbo-edition-xt1557-75x75-imaechsgw7ndcgdj.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>275x275</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/w/w/z/motorola-moto-g-turbo-edition-xt1557-275x275-imaechsgw7ndcgdj.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>125x125</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/w/w/z/motorola-moto-g-turbo-edition-xt1557-125x125-imaechsgw7ndcgdj.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>40x40</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/w/w/z/motorola-moto-g-turbo-edition-xt1557-40x40-imaechsgw7ndcgdj.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>1100x1100</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/w/w/z/motorola-moto-g-turbo-edition-xt1557-1100x1100-imaechsgw7ndcgdj.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>100x100</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/w/w/z/motorola-moto-g-turbo-edition-xt1557-100x100-imaechsgw7ndcgdj.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>200x200</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/w/w/z/motorola-moto-g-turbo-edition-xt1557-200x200-imaechsgw7ndcgdj.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>unknown</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/w/w/z/motorola-moto-g-turbo-edition-xt1557-original-imaechsgw7ndcgdj.jpeg</value></entry></imageUrls><inStock>true</inStock><maximumRetailPrice><amount>14499.0</amount><currency>INR</currency></maximumRetailPrice><productBrand>Motorola</productBrand><productUrl>http://dl.flipkart.com/dl/moto-g-turbo/p/itmecc4uhbue7ve6?pid=MOBECC4UZTSGKWWZ&amp;affid=kanakala8</productUrl><sellingPrice><amount>12499.0</amount><currency>INR</currency></sellingPrice><sizeUnit></sizeUnit><sizeVariants>[MOBECC4UQTJ5QZFR]</sizeVariants><title>Moto G Turbo Edition</title></productAttributes></productBaseInfo><productShippingBaseInfo/></productInfoList><productInfoList><productBaseInfo><productIdentifier><categoryPaths><categoryPath><item><title>Mobiles&gt;Handsets</title></item></categoryPath></categoryPaths><productId>MOBEDHZFWGKNJMHF</productId></productIdentifier><productAttributes><codAvailable>true</codAvailable><color>Black</color><colorVariants>[MOBEDHZFUZE9FTGB]</colorVariants><discountPercentage>0.0</discountPercentage><imageUrls><entry><key>400x400</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/m/h/f/asus-zenfone-max-zc550kl-6a023in-400x400-imaeegudewju56a8.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>275x275</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/m/h/f/asus-zenfone-max-zc550kl-6a023in-275x275-imaeegudewju56a8.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>75x75</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/m/h/f/asus-zenfone-max-zc550kl-6a023in-75x75-imaeegudewju56a8.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>125x125</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/m/h/f/asus-zenfone-max-zc550kl-6a023in-125x125-imaeegudewju56a8.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>40x40</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/m/h/f/asus-zenfone-max-zc550kl-6a023in-40x40-imaeegudewju56a8.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>1100x1100</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/m/h/f/asus-zenfone-max-zc550kl-6a023in-1100x1100-imaeegudewju56a8.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>100x100</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/m/h/f/asus-zenfone-max-zc550kl-6a023in-100x100-imaeegudewju56a8.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>200x200</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/m/h/f/asus-zenfone-max-zc550kl-6a023in-200x200-imaeegudewju56a8.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>unknown</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/m/h/f/asus-zenfone-max-zc550kl-6a023in-original-imaeegudewju56a8.jpeg</value></entry></imageUrls><inStock>true</inStock><maximumRetailPrice><amount>9999.0</amount><currency>INR</currency></maximumRetailPrice><productBrand>Asus</productBrand><productUrl>http://dl.flipkart.com/dl/asus-zenfone-max/p/itmedhzfdc6jhegv?pid=MOBEDHZFWGKNJMHF&amp;affid=kanakala8</productUrl><sellingPrice><amount>9999.0</amount><currency>INR</currency></sellingPrice><sizeUnit></sizeUnit><sizeVariants>[]</sizeVariants><title>Asus Zenfone Max</title></productAttributes></productBaseInfo><productShippingBaseInfo/></productInfoList><productInfoList><productBaseInfo><productIdentifier><categoryPaths><categoryPath><item><title>Mobiles&gt;Handsets</title></item></categoryPath></categoryPaths><productId>MOBEB3VWVWSEHBFD</productId></productIdentifier><productAttributes><codAvailable>true</codAvailable><color>Black</color><colorVariants>[MOBEB3VWZZTZSV5P]</colorVariants><discountPercentage>5.0</discountPercentage><imageUrls><entry><key>400x400</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/b/f/d/lenovo-vibe-p1m-pa1g0035in-400x400-imaec3g2ghmtg4vz.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>275x275</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/b/f/d/lenovo-vibe-p1m-pa1g0035in-275x275-imaec3g2ghmtg4vz.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>75x75</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/b/f/d/lenovo-vibe-p1m-pa1g0035in-75x75-imaec3g2ghmtg4vz.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>125x125</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/b/f/d/lenovo-vibe-p1m-pa1g0035in-125x125-imaec3g2ghmtg4vz.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>40x40</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/b/f/d/lenovo-vibe-p1m-pa1g0035in-40x40-imaec3g2ghmtg4vz.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>1100x1100</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/b/f/d/lenovo-vibe-p1m-pa1g0035in-1100x1100-imaec3g2ghmtg4vz.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>100x100</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/b/f/d/lenovo-vibe-p1m-pa1g0035in-100x100-imaec3g2ghmtg4vz.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>200x200</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/b/f/d/lenovo-vibe-p1m-pa1g0035in-200x200-imaec3g2ghmtg4vz.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>unknown</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/b/f/d/lenovo-vibe-p1m-pa1g0035in-original-imaec3g2ghmtg4vz.jpeg</value></entry></imageUrls><inStock>true</inStock><maximumRetailPrice><amount>8499.0</amount><currency>INR</currency></maximumRetailPrice><productBrand>Lenovo</productBrand><productDescription>Bring home the Lenovo VIBE P1m and enjoy an exceptional performance and long-lasting battery life. Battery Enjoy up to 16 hours of talk time and up to 20 days of standby time on the VIBE P1m, thanks to its long-lasting 3900 mAh battery. The OTG feature lets you use your Lenovo device to charge your other devices. Maximize Battery Life This device is equipped with a manual power saving switch that lets you extend battery life by disabling functions other than call, SMS and clock. Quick Charge Thanks to the Quick Charge function, you can quickly boost your device's battery by just plugging it in for a few minutes. Water-Resistant Build With the advanced splash-proof nano-coating inside and outside, your Lenovo device is engineered for protection against sudden drizzle and accidental spills. Display The Lenovo smartphone comes with a large 12.7 cm (5) HD IPS display. You'll love watching videos, browsing the Web and playing games on this device. Performance Thanks to the 64-bit Quad-core processor and 2 GB RAM, this Lenovo phone delivers a seamless and smooth performance. It runs on the Android 5.1 Lollipop operating system. Camera Click noteworthy photos and selfies with the 8 MP rear camera and 5 MP front camera of the VIBE P1m. Storage Store your favorite songs and apps in the 16 GB storage space offered by this device. You can expand the storage space to an additional 32 GB using a microSD card.  </productDescription><productUrl>http://dl.flipkart.com/dl/lenovo-vibe-p1m/p/itmecrurvpmzhcyg?pid=MOBEB3VWVWSEHBFD&amp;affid=kanakala8</productUrl><sellingPrice><amount>7999.0</amount><currency>INR</currency></sellingPrice><sizeUnit></sizeUnit><sizeVariants>[MOBEB3VWZZTZSV5P]</sizeVariants><title>Lenovo VIBE P1m</title></productAttributes></productBaseInfo><productShippingBaseInfo/></productInfoList><productInfoList><productBaseInfo><productIdentifier><categoryPaths><categoryPath><item><title>Mobiles&gt;Handsets</title></item></categoryPath></categoryPaths><productId>MOBE8AHAT4SFH3PJ</productId></productIdentifier><productAttributes><codAvailable>true</codAvailable><color>White</color><colorVariants>[MOBE8AHABTYGSZ2J, MOBE8AHAEG8GFCMX, MOBE9HPZNZRNFDZ2]</colorVariants><discountPercentage>0.0</discountPercentage><imageUrls><entry><key>400x400</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/z/2/j/lenovo-k3-note-na-400x400-imae8hstkr6sbtgt.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>275x275</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/z/2/j/lenovo-k3-note-na-275x275-imae8hstkr6sbtgt.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>75x75</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/z/2/j/lenovo-k3-note-na-75x75-imae8hstkr6sbtgt.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>125x125</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/z/2/j/lenovo-k3-note-na-125x125-imae8hstkr6sbtgt.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>40x40</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/z/2/j/lenovo-k3-note-na-40x40-imae8hstkr6sbtgt.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>1100x1100</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/z/2/j/lenovo-k3-note-na-1100x1100-imae8hstkr6sbtgt.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>100x100</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/z/2/j/lenovo-k3-note-na-100x100-imae8hstkr6sbtgt.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>200x200</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/z/2/j/lenovo-k3-note-na-200x200-imae8hstkr6sbtgt.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>unknown</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/z/2/j/lenovo-k3-note-na-original-imae8hstkr6sbtgt.jpeg</value></entry></imageUrls><inStock>true</inStock><maximumRetailPrice><amount>9999.0</amount><currency>INR</currency></maximumRetailPrice><productBrand>Lenovo</productBrand><productDescription>If you love watching movies or gaming on your smartphone, this sleek and powerful Lenovo K3 Note features a mesmerizing 13.97 cm Full HD display and is backed by powerful Octa Core performance. Display Enjoy watching videos, viewing high-resolution photos and gaming on the big 13.97 cm (5.5) Full HD IPS display of the K3 Note. With the 1920 x 1080 resolution, visuals come to life on this bright and vivid screen. Performance Thanks to the 64-bit Octa-Core processor, you can multitask effortlessly on this device. Apps, games and videos run smoothly and lag-free. This Lenovo device is powered by the faster and smoother Android Lollipop 5.0. Dual SIM Dual Standby Whether you travel abroad often or you want to separate business from pleasure, the Lenovo K3 Note offers you two SIM slots. GSM, WCDMA and LTE SIM cards are compatible with this device. With Dual Standby, both your SIM cards are active and you'll never miss important calls ever again. Battery Run an extra mile before you plug your Lenovo device into the power outlet. The powerful 2900 mAh battery packs enough punch for you to enjoy non-stop entertainment for longer. Storage With 16 GB internal storage, you can store more of your favorite photos, music and games worry-free in this Lenovo smartphone. Camera The K3 Note packs a 13 MP primary shooter which lets you capture amazing photos and videos. Sensors This Lenovo smartphone features a proximity sensor, gravity sensor, light sensor, anti gyroscope and an electronic compass. The gravity sensor and anti gyroscope let you enjoy flawless motion-based gaming.</productDescription><productUrl>http://dl.flipkart.com/dl/lenovo-k3-note/p/itmebygmmk8cfmy4?pid=MOBE8AHAT4SFH3PJ&amp;affid=kanakala8</productUrl><sellingPrice><amount>9999.0</amount><currency>INR</currency></sellingPrice><sizeUnit></sizeUnit><sizeVariants>[MOBE8AHABTYGSZ2J, MOBE8AHAEG8GFCMX]</sizeVariants><title>Lenovo K3 Note</title></productAttributes></productBaseInfo><productShippingBaseInfo/></productInfoList><productInfoList><productBaseInfo><productIdentifier><categoryPaths><categoryPath><item><title>Mobiles&gt;Handsets</title></item></categoryPath></categoryPaths><productId>MOBECCA5Y5HBYR3Q</productId></productIdentifier><productAttributes><codAvailable>true</codAvailable><color>Gold</color><colorVariants>[MOBECCA5SMRSKCNY]</colorVariants><discountPercentage>0.0</discountPercentage><imageUrls><entry><key>400x400</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/r/3/q/samsung-galaxy-on7-sm-g600f-400x400-imaecqkgzeuz9ebn.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>75x75</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/r/3/q/samsung-galaxy-on7-sm-g600f-75x75-imaecqkgzeuz9ebn.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>275x275</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/r/3/q/samsung-galaxy-on7-sm-g600f-275x275-imaecqkgzeuz9ebn.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>125x125</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/r/3/q/samsung-galaxy-on7-sm-g600f-125x125-imaecqkgzeuz9ebn.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>40x40</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/r/3/q/samsung-galaxy-on7-sm-g600f-40x40-imaecqkgzeuz9ebn.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>1100x1100</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/r/3/q/samsung-galaxy-on7-sm-g600f-1100x1100-imaecqkgzeuz9ebn.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>100x100</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/r/3/q/samsung-galaxy-on7-sm-g600f-100x100-imaecqkgzeuz9ebn.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>200x200</key><value>http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/r/3/q/samsung-galaxy-on7-sm-g600f-200x200-imaecqkgzeuz9ebn.jpeg</value></entry><entry><key>unknown</key><value>http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/mobile/r/3/q/samsung-galaxy-on7-sm-g600f-original-imaecqkgzeuz9ebn.jpeg</value></entry></imageUrls><inStock>true</inStock><maximumRetailPrice><amount>10990.0</amount><currency>INR</currency></maximumRetailPrice><productBrand>Samsung</productBrand><productDescription>Built for everyday entertainment, the sleek Samsung Galaxy On7 features an HD display, a Quad-Core processor and a powerful battery. Display Experience an immersive viewing experience with the On7 that boasts a 13.97 cm (5.5) HD TFT display. It delivers exceptional details, colors and tones for excellent visuals. MixRadio Get access to over 30 million tracks and free offline music with the preloaded music service MixRadio on this Samsung device. Long-Lasting Battery The 3000 m Ah battery lets you listen to your favorite tracks and browse through your favorite websites through the day without worrying about having to charge your phone. Fast Streaming &amp; Downloads Harness the power of 4G LTE and Wi-Fi on the Samsung Galaxy On7. Stream videos quickly and download more of your favorite content with data speeds up to 150 Mbps (on 4G LTE). You can also switch to Ultra Data Saving Mode (UDS) to save up to 50% of your 4G data while you stream, browse or download videos and content. Camera The On7 comes with a 13 MP rear camera and a 5 MP front camera. You can quickly launch this phone's camera by double tapping the home button from any screen. You can also take selfies quickly by showing your palm as a gesture. Performance With a Quad Core processor and 1.5 GB of RAM, the On7 delivers a seamless and lag-free performance. You'll love playing games, watching HD videos and multitasking on this Samsung device. This smartphone runs on Android Lollipop v5.1. Storage This Samsung phone comes with 8 GB of internal storage which can be expanded to an additional 128 GB using a microSD card.</productDescription><productUrl>http://dl.flipkart.com/dl/samsung-galaxy-on7/p/itmedhx3jgmu2gps?pid=MOBECCA5Y5HBYR3Q&amp;affid=kanakala8</productUrl><sellingPrice><amount>10990.0</amount><currency>INR</currency></sellingPrice><sizeUnit></sizeUnit><sizeVariants>[MOBECCA5SMRSKCNY]</sizeVariants><title>Samsung Galaxy On7</title></productAttributes></productBaseInfo><productShippingBaseInfo/></productInfoList></products></ns2:ProductSearchFeed>